week so pointing out not a lot of people got codecs and so it's that for me as a non-developer
what i realized at least at a small level like when building an mv product you don't have to be
a student at the beginning stages and bring it to sort of production ready status i'm talking
small application see i say your codecs is your let's say cursor is your product not sorry
the plot is your main development platform asking uh whatever the development platform is asking to
correct its own error when you're running that you get an error right yeah we face the same error
like solve this what is using a completely different ai tool which is going to scan them
tag code with right identify the gaps possibly identify the same error and that's all because
what i've been i've not tried to do a platform cross-computing every time i get a syntax error
or any kind of error i just paste it it will identify
what the cause is correct the code and often than not it always gives me what i'm looking for
which is the same and one right that's it that's a good question i think let me answer it and then
tell me if your answer is matching up what you're saying but um i primarily use codecs now i prefer
it it's a much easier experience and it's it's extremely good and it does a review on its own
work if it finds something then i will do the same i'll just get it to fix it because
it knows the code base it's focused on
that segment of the code and so what i like to do today i've got a second appeal because i know that
both of the platforms have strengths and weaknesses i shouldn't say weaknesses they're both really good
but some of the uh they're good at different things and sometimes when the models change
because the models seem to be changing like like two or three weeks it's either um chat gpt date
so i like this back and forth because as a non-dev it gives me this that if i was a
developer you know computer science crowd or whatever i probably just use one industry you
could that's worth everything just getting a second sort of i yeah my experience is like i'm
not right as i say competing each other but i try to build a similar scope within different platforms
yeah just look i'm a developer like that so i can see the code quality structuring and all yes uh
they are completely different if i'm trying to build similar structure into apps yes i like it's
the mindset you know like if i'm familiar with certain models if i were to change the model or
like in your case cross-compete you know i'm familiar with certain models if i were to change the model or like in your case cross-compete
yes often than not it's an endless loop right yes like i will never get to a satisfaction like both
will be with some stuff like we are good yeah because they're completely the thinking fellowship
is very different right yes so where to stop is for me like when the application runs and delivers
the way i need in terms of performance or the overall workflow that is what i think i can stop
and i can put into production right but if i were to use the same code to a different ai model and
identify how to improve upon and that process is going to be a little bit more complicated because
that process is going to be a little bit more complicated because
something which is still as i said it's an endless loop so in terms of value proposition
why would you compete two ai models with a completely different thinking philosophy
versus asking the same model who has written your code to solve the error that it is
see i would put this question back to you as a developer if you know that the models are
different if they have a different philosophy what is the opportunity the opportunity is to
spend five minutes and maybe it actually uncovers something that the modeling doesn't know but the
judgment that you don't have in the background so you'd be a better person to ask answer that
question but only after you try oh no too because this is like what you do yeah oh cool yeah as in
what am i building today yeah you're asking a question i'm using uh codex basic level uh script
oh and why did you ask great so um the submission name in discord channel if you haven't i highly
suggest you guys make a submission first we're going to go ahead and get started so i'm going to
work on you can continue tweaking your project until four but make the submission before that
so you don't miss a deadline okay so from 3 30 to 4 i will open this monitor for your testing highly
suggest you guys come and test your connection through your laptop because you are going to use
your laptop presentation it will be two minutes and uh we have some of our judges here so people
may come and ask around what do you build feel free to kind of like a q a so you get a first
impression from judges all right so and for the oh the mic bro all right so uh for the rest of
the uh categorized price like from the sponsors uh there will be sponsor judges
besides our judges to judge it so make submission online and i will share to sponsors like claude
and i believe kai will be on site to judge for the best use of codex and we do have other sponsors
online so make sure you make a submission before 3 30 and yeah so feel free to come to test your
laptop for the demo i will get back to you guys at four o'clock
for right any questions so far for submission any question all good cool all right so yeah
do you have less than an hour good luck guys