Here's a graph, again, of the artificial analysis intelligence index, which is, again, a benchmark that Big Show is going to focus on, that they're doing quite well on.
And this is a chart that I think is really interesting. It's intelligence versus output tokens.
So as you can see, GPT-5.5, Baud, and even Muse and Kimi are scoring quite well in the larger amount of tokens used.
So that's one of the reasons for the graph, and strong outputs.
There are some other interesting ones, like GPT-5.4 and 5, without reasoning, are very strong, so the amount of tokens they consume.
Also, Gemma 4 being only a 31-beam model showing up on the graph at all, I think is very interesting,
even though it uses a relatively large amount of tokens for its highest intelligence level.
You got a video?
There's a lot of those here.
The thing we can do is hit the ground running.
I'm going to ask how that's getting me ready for a search on Google Calendar, Gmail, Slack.
That gives me some free commands that I'm ready for my upcoming sales call.
That's the set of fully connected, useful, first workflow.
So yeah, I guess those basically show you what the UI is going to look like, especially when you're setting up plug-ins,
which, depending on what you're working on, can be super helpful.
I basically just want to go through how to get you set up, talk about some use cases,
and I've set up also a short workshop on using the API, which I've coded myself using the mobile app.
So some of the topics: introduction and setup, agents, how to delegate, some use cases, and then a few more advanced tips.
So this is just basically the history.
We started with code-complete, like copilot-type things, just finishing lines and suggesting words.
We've got two Parapro now.
It's able to do a whole task for you autonomously.
You still should be watching over it and checking up on it, but it's able to do a lot more now.
So there are three ways you can download it.
Make sure you're getting it from the official OpenAI source.
I do know that there's been some fake ones that have pulled up Google Ads, so just double-check that.
But you get the CLI, which I would recommend if you're on Linux.
It's pretty powerful and lightweight.
Codex App, which is really good for just direct use in Windows and Mac.
And then inside your IDE for a more integrated workflow
with your files, so you can directly edit things while you're going.
Here's just basically how to set it up.
There is the link and the install for the CLI.
You get it if you're in VS Code, just from the plugin section by searching Codex.
So to start, you want to open a repository.
You can also do it without one, just folderless.
But basically, it needs a folder to think about and to put files into, test them from, and so on and so forth.
I'll show you the agents one as an example.
This agents.md file is pretty important.
It is the, essentially, set of rules and instructions that you give the agents who knows how to update your codebase,
run your code, things like that.
You can also ask it to update these files with you as you go.
I essentially use it as a map to point it at the most important parts.
You just start with the prompt.
If you're not sure what you want it to do yet, I like to keep a to-do list and ask it, you know,
"What's new on the to-do list? What's something you can do yourself?
What's something that you think would be high value that you need me to check over?"
Stuff like that.
And so let's talk about the agents.
So it starts with a prompt, same as normal ChatGPT would.
And then it does the inference.
And it also runs tool calls, essentially just small snippets of code on your computer.
And it keeps doing that until it is satisfied and then it will respond to you.
At this point, it's often just the tool calls.
The response is not actually what you're looking for.
You're looking for the actions that it takes.
One thing to keep in mind is context.
When you run the prompt, ChatGPT will look at all of the information that it's fed.
So that would mean the agents.md as a start and anything it chooses to read, plus the prompt.
So yeah, it can hold a lot of text, like four to six hundred pages.
But some of these repositories and long workflows get a lot longer.
What it does now is compact the context after a while, which means basically writing a summary for itself.
It's very important to think about what you put in the context window because that is directly influencing the model's output from start to finish.
Sorry guys.
So Codex does manage the context.
Like I said, long conversations will lead to a bit of context drop where it gets confused and forgets things.
It does do its best here, but you do want to try to start a new conversation when you find things are going off the rails.
You can rely on this context window.
The context is automatically compacted, but only to a certain extent.
So yeah, when you work with Codex, you want to make sure that you're delegating, but you don't want to totally remove yourself from the process.
You need to make sure that you're learning and actually thinking about what you want and what makes a successful app, product, or whatever you're working on.
So yeah, start by building the perfect context, not the perfect prompt.
Remember, the prompt is just part of the context.
It's going to go through and it's going to search your codebase.
It might search external sources, things like that.
You want to make sure it's getting high quality information at every step.
Faster validation means better outcomes.
That means just checking stuff, getting a test signal itself, things like that.
Use the agent to learn, not vibe code.
If you're vibe coding, you want to make sure you're actually engaging with the process at every step.
So start with the goal.
Choose the files you want.
Like I said, you can bake these into your repo.
Strengths.
Tell it not to do certain things if you need.
And then give it an actual goal, because otherwise it'll just keep running forever and not really know what it's doing.
And it might decide it's finished before you want it to be.
And you can use plan mode.
You can get into that with shift app or slash plan.
And this will basically have it walk through a series of questions about your prompt in order to build a longer prompt for itself that you can review before you execute.
This is super useful, especially when I'm not sure what I want to do quite yet.
I have like a starter idea, but the details aren't quite filled in and they are still sensitive to, yeah, exactly what's running.
Use cases.
The learning of code base.
Especially helpful when learning about somebody else's code.
If you guys have been reading code a lot, it's one thing to read back your own code.
But reading somebody else's code can be a bit of an adventure.
This can help with that a lot.
Building plans like we just discussed.
Investigating changes instead of just going right ahead and implementing them.
And then taking in error logs and determining re-causes.
This is a really big one for me.
Making sure my apps are outputting information on what has happened so that I can go in and instead of having to guess,
call Codex, look at what happened, diagnose the error and suggest a fix.
It saves a lot of time for me and makes things a lot higher quality.
Review, which success, I believe that's as a skill.
Same with plans.
Something that I would do pretty regularly to make sure that your code is up to date and high quality as you keep moving forward.
And write documentation, which again is helpful for not just agents, but for users themselves and for yourself so they remember what you've been doing.
Writing tests with Codex.
I will say you might not want to write all of your tests with Codex.
It will sometimes write tests that are a little too easy to pass.
But it is very good at writing unit tests and to be honest, having simple tests is a lot better than having none.
You do want to review these to make sure they're achieving the actual goals you want.
But as you make changes, if you don't have a set of tests, there is no way of knowing if you've broken something while updating.
Which is going to happen a lot.
Using unit tests also helps with collaborating and like I said, remember to review it yourself.
So that it's a test you actually want to verify repeatedly.
And not just something that is because it is important.
It's essentially more about tests.
Again, the faster you're able to iterate on the step of the loop, you can move on to the next step on pounds pretty quickly.
That's why you want to define success deterministically.
Do that just like Codex.
Write the test and review it when you can.
Again, we've kind of seen this flow chart again.
This is more towards a team perspective.
Including tests, built-in steps, reviews between the actual team members or team agents.
Depending on your team size.
Making sure that you have documents and that it's deployed well.
Not sure anyone here is going to be deploying today, but it's good to keep in mind if you plan to scale.
Some more advanced concepts.
Standardized behavior with configurations.
I discussed agents.md.
I personally also keep a to-do list markdown file.
A to-do list that's managed by the agent.
A set of documentation that's managed by the agent.
A QA log.
What else?
Issue tracker as well.
A lot of these things can be handled through outside platforms like GitHub or Jira, but you can do it internally just using Textile.
Scale and distribute with skills.
So once you have a process that works, and this doesn't have to be specific to a repository, you essentially make, again, Textile.
It gets saved as a skill that's similar to the plug-ins for, say, Gmail that was shown at the beginning.
And then connect to your tools with apps and MCPs.
This would be for things like GitHub, like I mentioned, just connecting directly so that you don't have to go through the interface.
There'll be some things you want to put in the agents file.
A map of your code base.
Pitfalls that it might run into.
Keep updating as you go.
Any global contacts can be put in your user folders of agents.md.
It doesn't need to be just in your info.
It must pervade inside a subfolder so that as it goes through, if it's in that folder, it might find more info.
That would be, I guess, the overwrite thing.
For apps, again, we've touched on this a few times.
Desktop app support is a lot better now.
This is a little dated.
Building skills.
It starts with just a skill file.
You can add scripts.
Yes, yes, please.
Add a bundle for it.
Eventually, I guess, there is also plug-ins, which might be a plug-in and not a skill.
A skill is just the file, and then the plug-in is the whole bundle.
It's now called plug-ins.
It's on the video earlier.
So, to use the skill, you just want to do slash and then the name of the skill, and it will pop up.
You can mention it in plain language as well, but being specific helps a lot.
I would recommend maybe building a skill if you want to work with Codex.
Just ask it to make something.
And pick a task that requires access and structure that agents don't naturally have.
So, that might be connecting to this command line or an API.
Or it might just be adding, like, internal how-we-do-it-here rules.
Uh, guardrails, like compliance tagging or specific workflows for best practices.
I'm going to try to reconnect to the display and then get this workshop ready for you guys to present.
Because there is still time.
But as long as it's before 11:30, we can do that.
And then at 10:30, we can do that.
So, it's like a Discord.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
So, this is one of my get help pages.
I've got yours on.
I can hop into it here.
So, let me just start by telling you the most recent updates that I made on my phone.
So, I'm going to show you guys the latest updates.
So, let me just start by telling you the latest updates.
You can see the latest updates.