to host hackathon like 24 hours 48 hours even longer now we are able to host a hackathon within
eight hours so that's amazing so that's why i think like vibe coding brings a lot of people
from different industries a lot of experts um and even like non non-coder non-tech people join our
hackathons i'm so excited to see what you guys can build within a day using vibe coding if you
haven't like do any programming before that's fine we'll have a workshop teach you how to live code
today so you can learn and build in a day all right before that uh let's welcome kevin uh one of our
grand prize sponsor pack and he is going to give a quick remarks for today thank you very much uh
thanks jen uh thanks to the host and all the sponsors including myself and thanks to cozylab for having
thanks uh my name is kevin so uh when i was very young i fall in love with technology um since grade one
and grade two and um i played a lot of solitary and minesweeper but and i tried programming myself too
but my parents the conventional family they said hey you it's better to focus on the academic and they
kindly put my keyboard in a box and they put a lock on it so i couldn't enhance my programming career from
there however it's not an excuse it's not i'm not blaming my parents i love them um but it's a story
i kind of learned myself you do not give up you're going to be resilient so there's no reasons or
excuses for for anything um for doing what you love so with the technology today enables everybody to
become your own founder become your own entrepreneur and also a lot easier to make a product everybody can
become a super company yourself rather than having a many huge amount of people to work on a project we
can do a lot on ourselves nowadays too so interestingly enough i circle back my career into what real
estate and they currently were working on a data center project from turning a two megawatt legacy data center
into a upgrading and also uh retrofitting into a 10 megawatt ai computing facility in burgundy so
um uh that's also another uh small bit of a challenge i love to share with everybody to say here uh
when you build a product consider what is the use of the product what is the problem you're trying to
solve from day to day and to a more societal approach what is the problem to solve and also i try to ask
everybody to maybe consider the data layer um to to see like what is the best use of the of data and also
what could be a local computing scenario to use up the two to the 10 megawatt smaller data centers so
that's something i'd love to share with everybody and looking forward to see the product by the end of today
all right thank you thank you thank you all right so a little bit uh about a rundown i think you
are curious about it i try to simplify it give you more time to build uh so 10 30 we will have a team
up who haven't formed a team here oh a lot of okay cool so we'll do a team up at 10 30 and starting 11
you can start hacking actually you can start now i don't mind you start early but let's do it
just today okay we will have a codex workshop uh by kai uh do we have kai here yeah so kai will give
kai from kai is a codex uh ambassador in vancouver and he is going to give a codex workshop to you guys
at 11 and we'll have lunch today at 12 and a code review with ai workshop provided by adam adam's awesome
like teach you how to do code review with ai across different platforms using different models that'll be
awesome to code review before you submit and then at four uh it's submission deadline and there will be a
demo uh i will talk a little bit more about the demo and judging and then five o'clock at work very
compact day but i believe you guys can do it okay all right a little bit about cozy lab actually i would
like to introduce nick to give a quick introduction about uh cozy lab which is a space here it's awesome and yeah
thank you ian um thank you for having me so uh my name is nick lee i'm the owner for cozy lab so i'm
creating the space for all the young like entrepreneur talent in vancouver to collaborating and work
together in a no commitment and affordable price so and you can see we have over 23 rooms we open 24 7. so
people can just come here and uh you can just scan the qr code and the prices uh our cost is really cheap it's like 20 bucks
you can come here to use 24 hours so we have a complimentary coffee we have the oldest sparkling water and even beer or
or like uh tequila if you want yeah so yeah so so we just want to try to create a space in the central vancouver
and even if you want to book a room or like a monthly space like uh we are all available for everyone and
we have a front desk like working from 9 30 to 5 30 yeah so if you have a need for using the co-working
space just let me know thank you nick i think i need to host a beer hacks next time please you guys have
a beer and tequila hacks all right codex uh kai do you want to give a quick introduction about codex or
okay cool no problem i can help you to introduce it's just one word everyone knows okay so codex is
a coding agent that helps you build and shift with ai powered by chat dpt i think everyone is chat dpt
uh and codex is awesome i use it day today i really like it that's why we onboard codex on this hackathon
and there will be codex credit to you guys if you guys want to use it today and yeah we had kevin
introduced pack so i don't want to read it again but yeah just read it and thank you for pack uh for
sponsoring our event and cloud so it's cloud not clock but cloud is awesome and also a vancouver company
i don't know before this event so cloud provides a infrastructure to host open source models and it's
really cheap not i shouldn't use cheap it's cost efficient and you can run a lot of tokens with
like minimum price 60 percent cheaper token yeah this is cheaper but i'm fine with it okay cool so you
will get called um aki tokens today and i believe george from cloud has already standing instruction in
discord if you want to use it today i highly recommend you try it out and just sign up and get the 25
credit i i cannot spend 25 in a day actually so try it okay oh pro match so pro match is an ai
powered platform that is to make matching faster it's also one of our sponsor actually food sponsor
and it helps companies to do matching candidates clients teams and projects better so if you're
interested talk to me and i'm interested in introducing more about pro match to you and bravo okay so we have
representative for bravo okay if you haven't used bravo try that's my day-to-day use for chinese restaurants
actually so uh you can use amax to actually uh add credit to it and spend it you know amax you got a lot
of perks right so i use it every day and you get rewards uh what every time you're spending restaurants so
uh and today they are going to sponsor a 300 gift card you can spend in restaurants all right that's
pretty cool and elk is water so water over there it's awesome try it and if you need more uh let mike
know where's mike mike is gone okay that's fine so they sponsor a lot of like sports events in vancouver like
i think some like marathon events and uh i talked to mike and he's really interested in like working
with hackathons i i believe you need to drink more water when you're coding right so yeah coffee is
dehydrating but water you'll get it okay also community partners imp capital uh industrial ai
and uh triangle club we have we'll have mars here triangle club like we met at his space in um worry drive
it's awesome a good good place for lunch if you guys want to book a place for like a hell talk to mars
and alumify which is one of my students uh startup and they help uh lifelong learning so yeah talk to me if you're
interested in that cool a lot of people ask about it okay so now it's a theme your second brain is
interesting any idea coming out okay so today we're going to build ai that helps people remember
learn reason and act with the knowledge they already have all right think about it it can be software
any hardware anyone do a hardware hack today what kind of hardware like the house in the healthy part
house deck yeah okay cool yeah i do hardware hack i have tons of raspberry pi at home and uh yeah and
i hack on smart buses as well so if you need help with hardware or if you want to bring hardware hack let
me know i can mentor you or help you okay and judging criteria i will have four categories that judges will
look into uh innovation technology technical execution usability and the problem relevance i used to have
fifth which is go to market plan that's something that i really want to know but it's not a must if you
have that covered it will be bonus uh all right so take a picture on that i can close down this score
later but yeah i try to remember it so you should cover this in your submission since we have a lot of
people here and i want everyone to demo our project uh to the judges so each team has two minutes max
all right try to be an elevator pitch with a demo all right three things you want to show problem what
hurts demo what did you build a live demo i don't like a like a like a kind of fake demo a real demo
i really want to give the sum up for real demo uh impact why does it matter all right we want to make
impact all right grand prize 500 cash all right so i last time i see cash prices was in my
previous hack but yeah not a lot of hackers on offer cash price and thank you to our sponsor pack
and also 500 regular office space credit so they have an office space as well if you guys interest
and get that space on your wing uh and best use of codex we've got a hundred dollar token credit for
each team member all right if you have three people then 300 five people 500 right i recommend you form
large team so you can collaborate and learn from each other and gain what token best use of cloud 500
token and credit for the team all right so no matter how large is our team if you use cloud then if you
win it you got 500 all right best ai for lifelong learning that's my favorite because i teach uh bootcamp
so a full scholarship to write coding bootcamp by hack up actually i'm going to teach it if you are
are interesting go apply for that and best ai for physical commerce that's 300 gift card for bravo you
can use it today downstairs or somewhere around here with the bravo sticker on it you can just spend it
and bonus job price sponsored by uh access to order yeah there will be a draw price as well and winner will
get one of those 3d printed mathematical or avatar whatever i design it and i print it at home i hope
you like it all right uh this board again the last time i showed the discord get it okay cool all right
so uh before we begin the hack uh let's review conduct conduct respect include build honestly keep it safe ask for
help all right so everyone not first time hackathon right anyone here first time hackathon oh we got a
few all right so hackathon is more like a community event and i fall in love with since i'm in university
so that's why i keep doing it almost for free all right so um yeah try to follow the code of conduct if
you have any questions reach out to me or any staff here uh and all the staff here today are volunteers so
they yeah love pass to the staff here who make it happen thank you live coding and we are going to
start a team formation so if you don't have a team come to uh this room actually we have that room
opening and we can talk about your project and then form a team all right and then we will start the
we'll start the codex workshop at let's do it 10 30 so we can start early all right and we leave more
time for your hacks all right i will let you guys know the submission link in the discord channel there will be a link
uh you submit it uh i don't really like uh dev post i don't mean like it's not good it's a little bit too
complicated for a small scale hackathon we want to make it simple and then it probably will be just a
link and you submit your project and judges will come and make a job all right are you guys ready for
vibe coding today let's do it